Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Legislation, 1910 - 1990; 1961-1990; Series 4
  - Census legislative history (1/2), 1910-1980; Series 4 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Census legislative history (2/2), 1910-1980; Series 4 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Cesus Reapportionment Legislation (S.1734), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Comparisons of S.529 and HR.1510, 1983; Series 4 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Immigration Bill (HR.1061), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Congressional votes on Simpson-Mazzoli immigration bill, 1983 January; Series 4 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Congressinal voting analysis, 1987-1989; Series 4 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Congressional voting analysis on immigration, 1985; Series 4 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Constitutional rights for Aliens, 1987-1988; Series 4 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - DC human rights law, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Efficiency bills, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Efficiency bill amendments, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Efficiency bills and act, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Efficiency bills legislative language, 1989; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Employer sanctions bill, 1979; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Employer sactions (1/2), 1990; Series 4 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Employer sanctions (2/2), 1990; Series 4 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Equal Access to Justice Act, undated; Series 4 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Extended Voluntary Departure for Salvadorans (S.377), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Extended Voluntary Departure for Salvadorans, 1987; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Federal Unemployment Act, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Hearing, 1987 March 31; Series 4 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Hearing of house rules committee on HR.3810, 1986 September; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Hearing: implementation of immigration reform and control act of 1986, 1986 December 17; Series 4 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Hearing on S.332, 1987 June 18; Series 4 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - House subcommittee on immigration, refugees, and international law: general hearings on HR.3080, 1985; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - HR.3303, 1979; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - HR.3810 'triggered amnesty' amendment, 1985; Series 4 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - HR.4300 amendments, 1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - HR.4646, 1977; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - HR.5013, 1979; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - HR.5062, 1980; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - HP.5087, 1979 October 31; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Illegal immigration control act of 1985 (HR.2267), Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Immigration Act of 1985, Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Immigration and nationality acts legislative histories and related documents, 1950-1952; Series 4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Immigration and nationality acts legislative histories and related documents, 1952-1965; Series 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Immigration and nationality acts legislative histories and related documents, 1965-1978; Series 4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Immigration and nationality amendments of 1986 (HR.4823), Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Immigration and nationality amendments of 1986 (HR.4823), Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Immigration and nationality efficiency act of 1979 (S.1763), Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Immigration and nationality law, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Immigration Bill, undated; Series 4 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Immigration control and legalization amendments act of 1985 (HR.3080), Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Immigration control and legalization amendment act of 1985 HR. 3080, 1985 July 25; Series 4 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Immigration control and legalization amendments act (HR.3810), 1985; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Immigration control and legalization amendments act (HR.3810), 1985; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Immigration control and legalization amendments act (HR.3810), 1985; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Immigration exclusion and deportation amendments of 1985 (HR.2361), Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Immigration Exclusion and Deporation Amendments of 1987 (HR.1119), Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Immigration Law in 1984: a review of articles and cases, 1985 February 8; Series 4 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Immigration Reform Act (HR.2180) Congressman Roybal, 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1985 [1/3], Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1985 [2/3], Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1985 [3/3], Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Immigration reform and control act of 1986, 1986 October 14; Series 4 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Immigration reform and control act of 1986, Series 4 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (HR.3810) legislative history, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Increase in Immigrant Quota for Colonies and Dependent Areas (HR.1482), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Increase in Immigrant Quota for Colonies and Dependant Areas (S.737), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Code 2922, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1989-1990; Series 4 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1990; Series 4 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Legal immigration bills, 1990; Series 4 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Legislative History (1/2), undated; Series 4 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Legislative history (2/2), undated; Series 4 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Legislative History, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Legislative history: deportation and immigration, 1961; Series 1 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Legislative proposals, 1986 June 23; Series 4 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Legislation proposal: deportation, 1989 March 14; Series 1 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Mark up on HR.3080, 1985; Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Markup of HR.3810, 1986; Series 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Missouri Senate Concurrent Resolution No. 16, 1988 April 19; Series 4 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - No Amnesty Resolution (Res.184), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Oversight hearing, 1987 March 24; Series 4 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Oversight of IRCA S.322 mark-up, 1987 April 10; Series 4 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Panama canal commission bill, 1979; Series 4 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Proposals to reform immigration, 1988-1989; Series 4 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Proposed amendments to deportation proceedings and appeals, undated; Series 4 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Proposed amendments to refugee act of 1979 (HR.2816), Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Refugee Assistance Extension Act of 1985 (S.1262), Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Refugee act of 1979 (HR.2816), Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Refugee act of 1979 (HR.2816), Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Refugee act of 1979 and report in United Nations, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Refugee appropriations, 1990-1991; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Refugee assistance act (HR.2816), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Refugee assistance amendments of 1985 (HR.2286), Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Refugee Assistance Extension Act (HR.1452), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Refugee bill (S.643), 1980; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Resolution: approve 'Compact of Free Association' (HR.187/S.286), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Resolution: approve 'Compact of Free Association' (HR.187/S.286), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Resolution: cuban refugees (H.Res.339), 1980; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Resolution: limit immigration (Res.94), 1980; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Resolution: undocumented aliens and the census (Res.422), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ridge bill: ABA position, 1989 August; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Ridge bill: congressional record, 1989 August 1; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Ridge bill: Debruin statement, 1988 June 23; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Ridge bill: drafts for the suit, 1988; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Ridge bill: Dymally statement, 1988 September 27; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Ridge bill: hearing on HR. 2661, 1989 August 1; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Ridge bill: Keane statement, 1988 June; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Ridge bill: opinion of atty gen of Kansas, 1988; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Ridge bill: order granting joint motion, undated; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Ridge bill: proposed legislation, undated; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Ridge bill: public assistance and the IRCA, 1987 April; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Ridge bill: senate res 16, 1988; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Ridge bill: senate res 143, 1987; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Ridge bill talking points, undated; Series 4 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Safe Haven Act, 1988; Series 4 (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - SAVE Bill (HR.2626/S.1215), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - SAW provisions 8 CFR 210, undated; Series 4 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - SAW regulations, 1987; Series 4 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Search warrants (HR.3810), 1985-1986; Series 4 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Senate Subcommittee on Immigration and Refugee Policy on EVD for Salvadorans, 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Simin's hearing, subcommittee on justice and state, 1987 April 8; Series 4 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Simpson legal immigration bill, 1988; Series 4 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Shumer legal immigration reform bill, 1988; Series 4 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Simpson-Mazzoli Bill, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Statement on HR.907, 1981; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Summary of EVD Legislation in 100th Congress (S.332/HR.618), 1987; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Supplemental mark-up, 1987 March 10; Series 4 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - S.643 briefing meeting, 1979 August 30; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - S.643 congressional statements and reports, 1979; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - S.643 FAIR statements, 1979; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - S.643 Huddleston analysis and amendments, 1979; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - S.643 potential problems, unknown; Series 4 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - S.643 voting record and analysis, 1979; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - S.1157, 1979; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - S. 1200 and committee on the judiciary, 1985; Series 4 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Testimony on the construction of alien detention facilities, 1982; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Texas Articles 6663 and 6674, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - U.S. immigration court act of 1985 (HR.3187), Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - U.S.-Mexico border revitilization act of 1985 (HR.3199), Series 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - USA vs. Brignoni-Ponce, 1974; Series 4 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Visa preference systems S. 358, 1989 June; Series 4 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Voting records and memos on amendments (HR.1510), 1984; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Voting records and memos on amendments (HR.1510), 1984; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Voting records and memos on amendments (HR.1510), 1984; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Voting records and memos on amendments (HR.1510), 1984; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Fraud Bill (HR.1443), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - 8 CFR, undated; Series 4 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - 29 USCAs 651 and 31 USCAs 3729, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - 47 CFR 17757, undated; Series 4 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Court cases, 1867 - 1989; 1949-1989; Series 5
  This series contains the records of court cases. These cases cover the topics related to immigration. The records cover the dates 1867-1989 with the bulk of the records falling within 1949-1989.
  - Abate vs. Mundt, 1971 June 7; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Abudu vs. INS, 1986 October 14; Series 5 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Abourezk vs. Reagan, 1986 March 11; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - ACLU vs. Raburn county chamber of commerce, 1983 February 4; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - ACLU Georgia vs. Rabun county, 1983; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Acosta vs. Gaffney, 1977 July 5; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO vs. Brock, 1987 August 5; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Agarwal vs. Johnson, 1979 December 7; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Allen vs. Wright, Reagan vs. Wright, 1984 July 3; Series 5 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Allgood vs. Bradford, 1985 July 10; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Alonso vs. California, 1975 July 30; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Alvarado vs. Board of review, 1987 April 9; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Alvarez vs. Sanchez, 1984 November 7; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Alvarez vs. Sanchez, 1984 November 7; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Alyeska pipeline service co. vs. Wilderness society, 1975 May 12; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Amanullah Wahidullah vs. Nelson, Cobb, and Frank, 1987 February 4; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - American-Arab anti-discrimination committee vs. Meese, 1989 January 26; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee vs. Meese, 1989 January 26; Series 5 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - American baptist churches vs. Meese, 1987 March 30; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, 1989 July 24; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, 1989 August 14; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, 1989 August 14; Series 5 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, undated; Series 5 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh, 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh: brief, 1989 July 24; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh: brief, 1989 August 14; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh: drafts (1/2), 1989 August; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh: drafts (2/2), 1989 August; Series 5 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh: motions and applications, 1989 August; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (1/3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (2/3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (3/3), 1989; Series 5 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (1/4), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (2/4), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (3/4), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - American Friends Service Committee Corp vs. Thornburgh (4/4), undated; Series 5 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Amicus briefs (1/4), 1980-1981; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Amicus briefs (2/4), 1980-1981; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Amicus briefs (3/4), 1980-1981; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Amicus briefs (4/4), 1980-1981; Series 5 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Amicus briefs, undated; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Anderson vs. Celebrezze, 1983 April 19; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Anetekhai vs. INS, 1988 June 2; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Antillon vs. Department of employment, 1984; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Anwo vs. INS, 1979 June 19; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Aoun vs. INS, 1985; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Arizona vs. Mojarro Padilla, 1971 April 2; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Arp vs. Catholic diocese, 1987 March 17; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Artega vs. Literski, 1978 April 24; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Association dry good corp. vs. Equal employment opportunity commission, 1983 November 1; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Association of data processing service organizations vs. Camp, 1970 March 3; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Atkins vs. Parker vs. Block, 1985 June 4; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Avila-Murrieta vs. INS, 1985 April 9; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese brief, undated; Series 5 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (1/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (2/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (3/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (4/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (5/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (6/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (7/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Ayuda vs. Meese "known to the government" (8/8), 1988; Series 5 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Azizi vs. Meese (1/2), 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Azizi vs. Meese (2/2), 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Baker vs. Carr, 1962 March 26; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Baker vs. Wade, 1984 September 21; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Banks vs. Chicago grain trimmers, 1968 April 1; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Barber vs. Gonzales, 1954 June 7; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Barela vs. Superior court of Orange County, 1980; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Barenblatt vs. United States, 1959 June 8; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Barlow vs. Collins, 1970 March 3; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Bastas vs. Board of review, dept. of labor and industry, 1978 January 4; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Berger vs. Health and human services, 1983; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Berger vs. Heckler, Berger vs. Schweiker, 1985; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Bertrand vs. Sava, 1982 June 25; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Bhandari vs. First national bank, 1987 January 29; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Blake vs. Pallan, 1977 May 26; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Bonilla vs. Oakland scavenger co., 1982 November 9; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Borough of Bethel Park vs. Stans, 1971 September 30; Series 5 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Boston stock exchange vs. State tax commission, 1977 January 12; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Bowen vs. Roy, 1986 June 11; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Bradford vs. California, 1984-1986; Series 5 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Bradford vs. California, 1984-1986; Series 5 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Bradford vs. California, 1984-1986; Series 5 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Bradford vs. California: correspondence and media (1/2), 1984-1986; Series 5 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Bradford vs. California: correspondence and media (2/2), 1984-1986; Series 5 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Brennan vs. Steamfitters, 1974 May 21; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Bresgal vs. Brock, 1987 November 18; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Briscoe vs. Bell, 1977 June 20; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Brownell vs. Carija, 1957 December 5; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Buckley vs. Valeo, 1976 January 30; Series 5 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Burns vs. Richardson, 1966 April 25; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Burrafato vs. United States dept of state, 1975 August 13; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Cabell vs. Chavez-Salido, 1982 January 12; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Cady vs. Morton, 1975 June 19; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - California State Employees Assn vs. Kiddoo, 1987; Series 5 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Callahan vs. Woods, 1984 March 30; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Caminetti vs. United States, 1917 January 15; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Cardoza-Fonseca vs. INS, 1985 August 12; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Carey vs. Klutznick, 1981 June 12; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Carlson vs. Landon, 1952 March 10; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Carson vs. American brands inc., 1981 February 25; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Case law index, 1988 July; Series 5 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Cases against Law Books Ltd, 1987; Series 5 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Cases based on equal credit opportunity act, 1987; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Castillo-Felix vs. INS, 1979 July 30; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Social Services vs. Meese (1/3), 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Social Services vs. Meese (2/3), 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Social Services vs. Meese (3/3), 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Social Services vs. Meese, 1987 April 3; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Catrett vs. Johns-Manville sales corp, 1987 August 7; Series 5 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Census suit, undated; Series 5 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Census suit (1/3), 1981-1983; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Census suit (2/3), 1981-1983; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Census suit (3/3), 1981-1983; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Census lawsuit: bills, undated; Series 5 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Census lawsuit: Civiletti's ban on residential sweeps, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Census lawsuit: correspondence, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Census lawsuit: Cuban/Florida information, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Census lawsuit: correspondence and memoranda, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Census lawsuit: drafts and accompanying correspondence, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Census lawsuit: list of co-plaintiffs, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Census lawsuit: lower Manhattan, 1980 census, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Census lawsuit: mailing list, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Census lawsuit: memoranda, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Census lawsuit: McDade amendment correspondence, undated; Series 5 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Census lawsuit: proposed legislation, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Census lawsuit: questions and answers, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Census lawsuit: research, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Census lawsuit: summary of arguments, undated; Series 5 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Chae Chan Ping vs. United States, 1889 May 13; Series 5 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Chaline vs. Koch, inc., 1982 December 13; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Cheng vs. Gaf Corporation, 1984 October 25; Series 5 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Chevron USA vs. National resources defense council, 1984 June 25; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Chinese-American civic council vs. Attorney general, 1975 July 7; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Chryssikos vs. Commissioner of immigration, 1924 October 30; Series 5 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Church of jesus christ of latter-day saints vs. Amos, 1987 June 24; Series 5 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - City of Camden vs. Plotkin, 1978 October 31; Series 5 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - City of Lincoln vs. Ricketts, 1936 March 2; Series 5 (Box 84, Folder 1)